So how are you guys, today I am going to talk about something
from whom everyone passes, does not matter. You are male, female
or others. This is the time when you don't understand
whats going on, the brain is saying something else heart is saying something else, and the body
has got some different plans, all three are going in different directions
Today I am going to talk about puberty, now if I ask you people
What is puberty? Then most of you will speak, d*ck
gets bigger and testicles get big. Yes so right, as you write this your parent's education fees have been all recovered (Sarcastically). But many things are not written in books, and even if they are then who is reading them? Then come on let start
without any fooling around. Self-conscious. Before puberty children don't care
how they look. Knee's are swollen, teeth are crooked
soil in mouth and hair is all messed up
but from puberty when they come to there senses, the girls
first, use to fight on little things, now they like to get all dressed up
the girls which use to roam here and there
in marriages now are trying cat walk
the girls which use to pull each other ponies now they
share gossips, who is dating with whom, who is getting all ready
for whom, if you get to know these two things then your life
is successful, and the world's worst dangerous illness, posting photos with a black and white filter like they don't have anything to live for. I would rather panda emoji, something
about him makes me and who is that him and who are you talking about the neighbor Prakash
who jumps from his 1st floor, and you will think what will be worse than that
But no, the ghost of English climbs like tomorrow is a flight to England
you must have seen that most of the girl talk in English
Why? We have to look after our image too
which girl will you love the one who says "Hey, where are you going?" or
"Hey, Mukesh where are you going" (In Hindi). Now let's talk about the fool, idiot, and with no brains boys. The boys which use to play dangerous kabaddi
now they go to the gym. After coming from the first day of gym
will see themselves in the mirror-like they have achieved something great, there whole
the family name has been brightened and will pose like by looking them
Arnold himself will leap from the flying helicopter, these are my
biceps and triceps. (Dhinka chika) (Ref from a Bollywood film). After that hardening their stomach
they will post a photo with their malnutrition abs, and all comment section filled with boys replying "Amazing body bro
help me too for making abs ". This should be illegal swear to god. When they would return home
the whole body would have been filled with injuries, and their smell would fell like
shit from pig, but they have got deodorant and perfume
and to finish them in 1 week is a religious belief.
Now they have to start to apply the gel, that spikes shit is important. But no matter how much you
dip yourself in makeup, if you are shit you will be shit. Deal with it. Money & Show Off. Now you must be thinking of how puberty and money
are related. Now the kid going through puberty
he doesn't have more important that his image, like in Rockstar (Bollywood Movie)
they say "Image is everything and everything is image", everything matters to him
Where is he going to buy the shoes, Nike or Bata? Where is he going shopping
mall or Sarojini Nagar (market in India)? Where is he going for dinner restaurant or
Pappu dhabha. He measures everything in money he doesn't care about the quality
only it should be expensive. If you even give a magical yellow raincoat by saying it costs 4500INR, he will wear it happily. If the kid has an interest in sports then he wants the most expensive, even if he doesn't know how to play but with the bat
the bat should have an MRF sticker on it. If he has an interest in football then he will wear only the shoes
who has Nike written on it. Shoes don't matter to him he just wants that 8000INR Nike on it.
And football he wants Jabulani, which was used in the world cup. Like sisterf*cker will become Ronaldo tomorrow. During puberty in human, a bad and important thing take place called ego and show off
From PSP to dad's costly car, all show off is mandatory. Just think 14-year old whose name is Padu Padoda
his father brought Audi, see his Audi a*s torn. Now Padu Padoda
In his 14-year-old life as many insects, human, monster, and devil
he knows he will them all. When you will meet him
Somebody:- How are you? Padu:- Nothing, bro I just bought Audi. Somebody:- Oh congrats bro, OK listen
Somebody:- Will come at noon for playing? Padu:- No bro, at noon I have to go to the salon in Audi.
Somebody:- Then in the evening? Padu:-Not in the evening, I will go to the gym in Audi.
Somebody:- Then at tuition? Padu:- No bro, I will go see Qutub Minar in Audi. Just shut the f*ck up. No, I don't understand
your father bought your father
paid for it your father will drive it you didn't do shit
still telling everyone i bought Audi i bought Audi
I bought an Audi. Anyway, your father bought it so you have full right on it
but what so much to show off. He bought a car, not a f*ucking country. Superiority & Aggression. The amount of attitude you will find in 13-14 year old kid
will be more than two 70-year-old men combined.
Every kid looks at the kid of his age and thinks
he is f*cker. If you look at this from this perspective, all the children are f*ucker then.
And they proved this themselves. They live in their world
where they think are at the top and all others below them. While thinking the
even pick their nose. These people are that weird. You can
crash their scooter, they will say nothing. But if you take a piece of their pizza then
their soul's trembles. And when next day you again take their pizza
the piece, they will say nothing. But if you crash their scooter then
then will try to kill you. What do you want from life, what will you settle on. Now this
must have happened in the class with many of you. Head must be rotating randomly and
then you see your crush, love and they get lost
in their imaginary world. From Aashiqui till Jism 2 everything is done. Then you suddenly listen
Teacher:- Padu Padoda stands up and answer this question. Padu:- Sir, can I give while sitting? Teacher:- No, stand up and answer this question. Padu:- No sir I can't stand, can I answer while sitting.
Teacher:-  Padu Padoda stands up. Friend:- When you know the answer why are you not standing? Padu:- My d*ck is erect bro. (Friend Laughing) Teacher:- You, why are you laughing (Friend Gulping) stand up and answer this question. Friend:- Sir can I also sit and answer?
Padu:- You also know the answer then why are you not standing?
Friend:- Bro my d*ck is also erect. (Khadha hai song) According to my worthless survey this incident
happens to every 100000 to 200000 boys. The world thinks girls are very
smart, quickly stand up and answer. It's not like that we don't
know the answer, just we can't stand. Conclusion. Now you people will say
if you have shared this info then tell the solution too.
See it's not a disease that can be cured. This happens to everyone.
It's natural. Natural f*cker. So you don't need to take it
seriously. Make fun. Enjoy Life.
And if you liked this video then click the like button.
And If you want more video like this then let me know in comment section.
And you saw it for the first time and enjoyed it then subscribe to CarryMinati.
Smash the like button shake it do anything but it should be clicked.
Now I will also go, I have to see Praksh jump from the 1st floor. Ok Bye. Subtitle From @SubtitlePortal (Instgram)
Subtitle From @SubtitlePortal (Instgram)